Sillitoe mss. II, 1950-1996 LMC 2141
Lilly Library
- III. Miscellaneous (Box 25)
  - CLIPPINGS (Box 25-27)
    Contains news clippings of articles both by and about Sillitoe, as well as of reviews of his works.